{
    "subject": "resource/Esso_Atlantic_class_supertankers",
    "predicate": "ontology/builder",
    "object": "resource/Hitachi_Zosen_Corporation",
    "human_readable": "The Esso Atlantic class supertankers were built by Hitachi Zosen Corporation.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9550749659538269,
            "question": "By which company were the Esso Atlantic class supertankers constructed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9274766445159912,
            "question": "Who built the Esso Atlantic class supertankers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6884948015213013,
            "question": "Is Hitachi Zosen Corporation known for shipbuilding?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5288057923316956,
            "question": "How large are the Esso Atlantic class supertankers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4518769383430481,
            "question": "Are there any notable features of the Esso Atlantic class design?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44226399064064026,
            "question": "What type of vessels are the Esso Atlantic class?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4328106641769409,
            "question": "What materials are typically used to build supertankers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3485502004623413,
            "question": "What are some common uses for supertankers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3332253098487854,
            "question": "What is the significance of the name 'Esso' in relation to these tankers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04224034771323204,
            "question": "What is another name for a supertanker?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Esso Atlantic class supertankers were built by Hitachi Zosen Corporation.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1857_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of the name 'Esso' in relation to these tankers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1857_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common uses for supertankers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1857_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What materials are typically used to build supertankers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1857_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1857_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1857_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1857_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1857_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1857_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1857_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1857_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1857_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1857_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1857_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided documents state that the Esso Atlantic, a supertanker, was built by Hitachi Zosen Corporation. Therefore, the statement \"The Esso Atlantic class supertankers were built by Hitachi Zosen Corporation\" is supported by the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}